<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scott Gallant on Forestry.io</title>
    <link>https://forestry.io/authors/scott-gallant/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scott Gallant on Forestry.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 12:38:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://forestry.io/authors/scott-gallant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Pricing</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/new-pricing-organization-accounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 12:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/new-pricing-organization-accounts/</guid>
      <description>We’re excited to announce new pricing!
Now, the Personal plan supports unlimited sites and up to 3 free Guest users per site (a “Guest” is a single-site user with limited permissions, similar to an “editor”). The Business plan also supports unlimited sites, but is designed for larger teams who need to manage many users across their sites and branches. Finally, our Enterprise plan is designed for large organizations with special requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Media Management</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/introducing-media-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 11:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/introducing-media-management/</guid>
      <description>We all love working with Markdown but one of it&amp;rsquo;s biggest limitations is adding images to your content. That&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the Forestry.io Media Manager. Nolan and Nichlas put a lot of work into crafting an amazing UX for this, so we hope you like it. --
Media Manager Drag multiple files Handy if you have large image galleries.
Manage other files Also manage non-image files like PDFs, text files, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 27th Service Outage</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/march-27th-service-outage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 21:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/march-27th-service-outage/</guid>
      <description>As some of you may have noticed, Forestry was down for about 2.5 hours between 23:00 UTC March 27 until 01:30 UTC March 28. In the spirit of full disclosure I&amp;rsquo;d like to explain what happened and why.
Forestry is a Rails application and from time to time the number of migrations we have get unwieldy. Being an application under rapid development, things are constantly changing and migrations are created sometimes daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customize the UI with Front Matter Templates</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/front-matter-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 10:47:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/front-matter-templates/</guid>
      <description>Does the following sound familiar? You set up a WP site, hand it off to a non-dev, and then they point to some unused part of the UI and say:
 &#34;What does this do?&#34;
 To which you sheepishly reply:
 &#34;Oh, that doesn&#39;t do anything...just ignore it.&#34;
 A CMS often feels like a work-around, designed for some other purpose.
Front Matter Templates (FMTs) FMTs allow you to customize the presentation of your UI fields in your CMS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Forestry.io</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/the-new-forestry-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 19:36:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/the-new-forestry-io/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce some huge improvements to Forestry.io, our CMS for Jekyll and Hugo sites.
Before I outline what&amp;rsquo;s new, I want to thank everyone who has been testing this while it was in beta (you know who you are). Your help was crucial and we&amp;rsquo;re going to continue to build an awesome CMS that you love. 👊
What&amp;rsquo;s new: New Editor We totally rebuilt our WYSIWYG editor (inspired by Medium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forestry.io &#43; Techstars 2016</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/forestryio-techstars-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 19:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/forestryio-techstars-2016/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re stoked to announce that Forestry.io is going to be part of Techstars NYC. The 90-day program runs from July until the end of September 2016.
What this means for Forestry and our users:
 We&amp;rsquo;re going to be surrounded by some of the brightest minds in New York tech We get to focus intensly on making Forestry awesome for our users. Stoked to be working 15-hour days! Over $1,000,000 in amazing &amp;ldquo;perks&amp;rdquo; (free stuff) from companies such as Amazon, Digital Ocean, Microsoft, Google, Sendgrid, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why we built Forestry</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/why-we-built-forestry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/why-we-built-forestry/</guid>
      <description>My friend, Emily, needed a simple website for her restaurant. She&amp;rsquo;s a chef and didn&amp;rsquo;t want to deal with the hassle of DNS, hosting, design, etc. As a recovering freelancer, I offered to help.
Normally, I would use WordPress for a site like this, but I was fed up with the headaches that comes with maintaining a WordPress site. So, I took an evening and cranked out a simple 1-page static site.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>