<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Frequently Asked Questions on Forestry.io</title>
    <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Frequently Asked Questions on Forestry.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Cancel/Downgrade a Per-Site Plan?</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/cancel-legacy-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/cancel-legacy-plan/</guid>
      <description>To cancel a legacy plan (e.g. the Team Plan) navigate to your dashboard and click on the &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; next to your site name. From there, select &amp;ldquo;Downgrade Plan&amp;rdquo; in the dropdown.
Please read the warning carefully and if you&amp;rsquo;re certain you want take this action please click on &amp;ldquo;Downgrade&amp;rdquo;.
Please note that when you downgrade a plan you can&amp;rsquo;t have more than 3 Users on a site unless a site is inside an Organization - see Team Management</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Transfer a Site to an Organization?</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/transferring-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/transferring-site/</guid>
      <description>Navigate to a site on your Dashboard (e.g. &amp;ldquo;My Sites&amp;rdquo;). Click on the &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; next to a site and select &amp;ldquo;Transfer Site&amp;rdquo; in the dropdown. On the next screen you can choose between &amp;ldquo;My sites&amp;rdquo; or an &amp;ldquo;Organization&amp;rdquo;.
If you selected &amp;ldquo;Organization&amp;rdquo;, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to choose the destination from the dropdown menu, once you made your decision click on &amp;ldquo;Transfer&amp;rdquo;.
ROLESYou can only transfer sites to Organizations if your role for that Organization permits it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CI/CD</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/glossary/ci-cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/glossary/ci-cd/</guid>
      <description>Continuous Integration (CI) Continuous Integration (CI) is a development practice where developers check-in code to a version control tool multiple times per day. Each time code is checked-in, an automated build is performed, allowing developers to identify problems with code quickly.
Continuous Delivery (CD) Continuous Delivery (CD) is a development practice where developers produce software in short cycles, ensuring that software can be easily released at any time. This ensures that developers are producing quality code and are identifying problems quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Files</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/glossary/content-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/glossary/content-files/</guid>
      <description>Content files are files that are processed by your static site generator and output in a different format (usually .html).
They are usually Markdown files (.md, .markdown) or HTML files (.html).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front Matter</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/glossary/front-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/glossary/front-matter/</guid>
      <description>Front matter is structured metadata that is stored at the top of a content file, and is identified by delimiters before and after the metadata.
This metadata is available to your templates when generating your site, and allows you to build robust, dynamic features into your static site.
Depending your static site generator, Front Matter can be formatted as YAML, TOML, or JSON.
Examples YAML --- title: My New Post date: 2018-07-01 04:00:00 +0000 images: - /uploads/2018/07/01/twitter_card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I backup my site?</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/backups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/backups/</guid>
      <description> For developers, backups are inherent due to the Git-backed nature of Forestry. Every change made to your site through Forestry is stored in version control.
However, a zip backup of your site can be downloaded from the dashboard if necessary.
Steps  Navigate to the dashboard Click the ... button beside the site you wish to download a backup of Choose &amp;ldquo;Download&amp;rdquo; from the menu  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do I set fallback/hidden values for Front Matter?</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/front-matter-fallbacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/front-matter-fallbacks/</guid>
      <description>Adding Front Matter to your content allows you to add variables and configuration to your pages that can be used in your templates.
Often times, you will find that you are repeating the same front matter values across many files. For example, setting the same layout, or adding the same author across many posts.
Or you may want to provide a default value for optional fields.
In this scenario, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to provide a fallback or hidden value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Files</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/glossary/static-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/glossary/static-files/</guid>
      <description> Static files are files that are not processed by your static site generator. Instead, they are just copied over as-is at built time.
Examples  Jekyll: in Jekyll, this is any file without front matter. Hugo: in Hugo, this is any file in the staticDir, which defaults to static/  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Site Generators</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/glossary/static-site-generators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/glossary/static-site-generators/</guid>
      <description> Static Site Generators are developer tools that convert various data formats into static sites.
These data formats are generally content files stored in a Git repository. They can also be data pulled from third-party services.
Examples  Jekyll is the static site generator written in Ruby and created by GitHub founder, Tom Preston Werner. Hugo is the static site generator written in GoLang and created by Steve Francia.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Sites</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/glossary/static-sites/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/glossary/static-sites/</guid>
      <description>Static sites are websites built using static, unchanging files. They require no server processing time to deliver the content to the user, which makes them very fast and performant.
Static site generators are the modern way of building static sites. They convert simple, text-based content files in static files ready for the web.
They’re fantastic for developers because they are extremely fast, are built to work with version-control, and require little-to-no setup compared to existing monolithic CMS solutions like Wordpress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What versions of Hugo do you support?</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/hugo-version/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/hugo-version/</guid>
      <description> We strive to always supports the previous 3 major versions of Hugo with their latest patch. (e.g, x.3.x, x.2.x, x.1.x).
Backwards compatibility is always available for sites using an older version of Hugo that was supported when the site was added to Forestry.
Note: Forestry does not provide immediate support for Hugo releases.
Other Software We also support the following software that is supported by Hugo:
 asciidoc asciidoctor pandoc  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What versions of Jekyll do you support?</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/jekyll-version/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/jekyll-version/</guid>
      <description>Forestry will use whatever version of Jekyll is specified in your Gemfile.
If you don’t specify a version in your Gemfile, Forestry will use the default version used by GitHub Pages.
Defaults These are the ruby gems that Forestry will bundle with your build by default, without the need for a Gemfile. Forestry also lets you specify different versions of gems by including a Gemfile with your site.
 activesupport (4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Forestry add files to my repo?</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/forestry-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/forestry-files/</guid>
      <description>Why did you add a .forestryio file? We add a file called .forestryio to the root of your project.
This file notifies Forestry that you have previously published to this location and that it is safe to publish to this location again.
Why did you add a .forestry folder? We add a folder called .forestry to the root of your project with the code configuration of your site.
This enables developers to edit the configuration of the CMS in their local environment, and keep changes to the configuration in version control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why did Forestry edit my files?</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/forestry-changed-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/forestry-changed-code/</guid>
      <description>As devs, we hate when people mess with our code. So we try to do this as little as possible but sometimes it is unavoidable.
Front Matter Forestry will remove comments and other formatting from front matter, and will also reorder your fields alphabetically. This is unfortunately unavoidable, as comments and order are not respected in the YAML or TOML specifications.
Newlines New lines will be normalized so that all line endings are the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guests</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/guests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 10:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/faqs/guests/</guid>
      <description>A Guest is a single-site user with limited permissions. Guests do not get access to support and are often used for clients or external colleagues.
A Guest can only access the site that you invite them to, whereas your team (available to those on the Business Plan) can access all of your sites.
Each site can have up to 3 Guest accounts.
For more information on managing Guests, see Team Management.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>