<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pnyv dot sh</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on pnyv dot sh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>pnyv dot sh</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Details Matter- UX Microcopy for Svbtle</title>
      <link>/blog/detailsmatterone-svbtle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/detailsmatterone-svbtle/</guid>
      <description>Details Matter 001: Svtble -&amp;gt; Before settling on a configuration utilizing Hugo and Netlify in order to serve this site up to you readers, I admittedly hopped around on my blog-wagon, jumping from one platform to the other- be it WordPress, Ghost, Jekyll, Grav, Postach.io or even the likes of Squarespace, Wix and Webflow.
During my &amp;ldquo;tours,&amp;rdquo; I stumbled across a rather eye-catching platform- (you guessed it) Svbtle. The reason I choose to write this first post dedicated to Svbtle&amp;rsquo;s inconsistencies in the UI / UX decisions is because had Svbtle accepted Debit Cards, you would&amp;rsquo;ve been looking at a Svbtle blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Ways to Handle Forms on Your Static Site</title>
      <link>/blog/talkingaboutredundancies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 03:30:13 -1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/talkingaboutredundancies/</guid>
      <description>When I first started exploring the potential of static sites, I was attracted by their speed and simplicity. I knew these benefits came at a cost, however: since static sites can’t run backend code, there are limits to what you can accomplish with a static solution.
I no longer see things this way.
JAMStack is not about sacrificing features for the sake of a performant, easy to maintain website. Rather, it is about re-evaluating how much of your desired functionality should be delegated to your web frontend.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>