<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cms on Forestry.io</title>
    <link>https://forestry.io/categories/cms/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cms on Forestry.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 14:00:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://forestry.io/categories/cms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>uBuild: A New Jekyll Theme Using Blocks</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/ubuild-a-new-theme-for-static-sites-using-blocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/ubuild-a-new-theme-for-static-sites-using-blocks/</guid>
      <description>Back in April we announced a feature that we believed was a game-changer for static site content managers. Blocks was here to introduce a way for you to put together sites using pre-composed site snippets inside Forestry.
While we did our best to show you how to set them up and give you an idea of how powerful they could be, we noticed that getting to know Blocks and figuring out how to set them up from scratch wasn&amp;rsquo;t as self-explanatory as we had hoped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Support for All Versions, Sorting for Pages and more</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/hugo-support-sorting-for-pages-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 23:32:20 -1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/hugo-support-sorting-for-pages-and-more/</guid>
      <description>We just made a big change to how we handle Hugo projects and introduced a few new features that make it easier to stay organized.
Hugo Support for All Versions 🔥🔥🔥 Hugo has a great developer community that is constantly pushing new versions out. Until now you sometimes had to wait a few months until you were able to use the latest version of Hugo with Forestry as we were trying to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Renaming Files and Improving Editing in a Team</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/renaming-files-and-improving-team-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 04:39:03 -1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/renaming-files-and-improving-team-editing/</guid>
      <description>It’s a cloudy day ☁️ here on Prince Edward Island, the perfect opportunity to announce some new features.
Over the past couple weeks, we were hard at work to improve the editor experience for our Git-backed content manager. Renaming files is just one of those updates. We also needed to improve notifications and indicators to make working in a team on Forestry easier.
Renaming Files ✍️ Freshly out — you can now change the name for your content files with Forestry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudinary Integration, Data File Templates and Other Features</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/cloudinary-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 15:12:40 -1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/cloudinary-integration/</guid>
      <description>Image Transformation and Responsive Image Delivery Today we&amp;rsquo;re proud to announce an easy way to optimize your image delivery with a Cloudinary integration for Forestry.
As a developer you can now use the super fast Cloudinary CDN and store your assets outside your repository. While at the same time your editors can use Forestry&amp;rsquo;s Media Library and Editor to upload and manage Cloudinary assets without even knowing it.
It&amp;rsquo;s as simple as adding your cloud name, API key and secret to your site&amp;rsquo;s settings to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blocks - Give Your Editors the Power to Build Pages</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/blocks-give-your-editors-the-power-to-build-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 14:41:00 -1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/blocks-give-your-editors-the-power-to-build-pages/</guid>
      <description>Today we introduce Blocks - a powerful Field Type that enables your editors to build entire landing pages from scratch and create rich blog post layouts with a pre-defined code template, we call it a Block Template.
This feature was inspired by CraftCMS&amp;rsquo; Matrix fields and the Wordpress Plugin Advanced Custom Fields.
What is Blocks? Blocks is a Field Type that is made up of multiple templates, so-called Block Templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML File Contents are Moving to Plaintext Editor</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/discontinuing-wysiwyg-editor-new-focus-on-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 21:57:29 -1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/discontinuing-wysiwyg-editor-new-focus-on-markdown/</guid>
      <description>We are not changing or removing the Markdown WYSIWYG editor. Our Markdown editor will continue to offer both plaintext and WYSIWYG input modes. In fact, removing the HTML WYSIWYG editor will allow us to focus on making the Markdown editor even better.
 The HTML WYSIWYG Editor has proven to be less and less the state-of-the-art content editing experience it once set out to be. Considering the issues the HTML WYSIWYG Editor causes and the merits Markdown provides we made the decision to discontinue our WYSIWYG HTML Editor on 5/11/2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018/04/09 Changelog</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/changelog/2018-4-9-changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/changelog/2018-4-9-changelog/</guid>
      <description> Hugo Support for v0.38.1 We updated our support to Hugo v0.38.1 and below. See Hugo News
Bug Fixes  Documentation: Links to documentation were updated Github Authentication: Increased timeout length and added a more descriptive message on timeout Import: Fixed a bug that prevents a complete list of repositories being listed for Bitbucket users Import: Fixed a bug that prevents import if the config filename was provided in the import path Media: White images can now be detected in the Media Library Notifications: Team members of an Organization now receive notifications without having to refresh the page Redirect: Removing a site from an Organization does not redirect to My Sites anymore UI: Fixed cropping of icons in CMS sidebar UI: Added a more descriptive explanation to the repo step in the starter template flow User Roles: Manage Guests is now unavailable to Guests of a particular site  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Pricing</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/new-pricing-organization-accounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 12:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/new-pricing-organization-accounts/</guid>
      <description>We’re excited to announce new pricing!
Now, the Personal plan supports unlimited sites and up to 3 free Guest users per site (a “Guest” is a single-site user with limited permissions, similar to an “editor”). The Business plan also supports unlimited sites, but is designed for larger teams who need to manage many users across their sites and branches. Finally, our Enterprise plan is designed for large organizations with special requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018/01/29 Changelog</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/changelog/2018-1-29-changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 14:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/changelog/2018-1-29-changelog/</guid>
      <description>Bug Fixes  Front matter template: Fix for hidden fields showing in field groups or repeatable field groups. Front matter template: Front matter templates can create a duplicate upon saving. Pages: Clarified copy surrounding unsaved changes on a document. Pages: Linking to a page that a teammate is editing is now handled properly. Pages: Deleting a page from the page form no longer shows &amp;ldquo;Connection Lost&amp;rdquo; modal. Editor: Fixed issue with emphasis and code deleting the next character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changes &amp; Improvements to the Media Library</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/a-new-and-improved-media-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 04:00:00 +1400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/a-new-and-improved-media-library/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve got great improvements to share with you from Forestry.io, involving Forestry’s Media Library.
The Media Library allows content editors to easily upload images, videos, and much more without needing to understand Git.
Single Upload Directory We&amp;rsquo;ve received a lot of feedback from the community about which media should be displayed in the media library.
Forestry used to display media from all folders throughout the project. Not all of these folders are useful for your editors, and resulted in theme assets, favicons, and other media being displayed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018/01/09 Changelog</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/docs/changelog/2018-1-9-changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 15:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/docs/changelog/2018-1-9-changelog/</guid>
      <description> Bug Fixes  Front matter template: fix for editing/unediting FMT fields didn&amp;rsquo;t always update the UI git deploy settings: Clarified copy surrounding the Deploy on Git Push feature. inline code: input rule for inline code no longer marks up the previous character.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discontinuing Zip-imported Sites</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/discontinuing-zip-sites/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 14:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/discontinuing-zip-sites/</guid>
      <description>Letting developers import a site from a zip archive is a feature that a lot of our users have made use of. However, with our strong focus on Git-backed workflows, we feel that that sites imported with zips have been providing a unsatisfactory experience.
At Forestry, we believe Git-backed content management systems are the future of content management, and that using a Git repository is the best way to manage sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Forestry Config Files</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/introducing-forestry-config-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 16:09:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/introducing-forestry-config-files/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Forestry Config Files Last month we released a big update to Front Matter Templates, which provided an unprecedented level of control over the user interface content editors use to edit their Hugo and Jekyll sites with.
Today we’re introducing a new feature to equally empower developers: Forestry Config Files.
Config files allow developers to create and manage the settings and Front Matter Templates of a site directly in the Git Repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WYSIWYG Formatting in Front Matter</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/wysiwyg-formatting-in-front-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 11:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/wysiwyg-formatting-in-front-matter/</guid>
      <description>This week we’ve got a small, but very useful update we&amp;rsquo;re excited to share with you.
WYSIWYG Formatting in Textareas Our textarea Front Matter field has been upgraded to allow for WYSIWYG input. Enjoy being able to add bold, italic, underline, and code formatting.
Enable WYSIWYG for Textareas You can enable the WYSIWYG features by enabling the “WYSIWYG” toggle on any textarea Front Matter field.
Give Us Feedback While the WYSIWYG features are inline only right now, we’re looking to develop this field into a truly powerful tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Improvements to Front Matter Templates</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/big-improvements-to-front-matter-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 10:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/big-improvements-to-front-matter-templates/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve got great improvements to share with you from Forestry.io, involving Forestry’s Front Matter Templates.
Front Matter Templates allow you to customize the UI of your front matter fields in Forestry, providing the tools necessary to create the exact CMS you need.
Improved Editing Experience Forestry&amp;rsquo;s Front Matter Template editor is now two-paned. A preview of your fields is on the left, giving you a realistic preview of how they will appear when editing content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improved Collaboration &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/improved-collaboration-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 16:30:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/improved-collaboration-and-more/</guid>
      <description>Document Locking &amp;amp; Collaboration To prevent accidental overwrites and the tango of content editing, we’ve added in a locking feature to your content and data files. If you attempt to edit a page another user is editing, you’ll get a notification.
We’ve also made collaboration more powerful by making drafts shared. If you make changes to a document without publishing, the rest of your team will see these changes when they view the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Layout Improvements</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/layout-improvements/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 09:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/layout-improvements/</guid>
      <description>We’ve been hard at work this month at Forestry.io, focusing on improving the editing experience and overall usability of the application and we’re excited to announce that it’s already here! We’ve got 3 updates to share with you that will make using Forestry much more enjoyable.
New Editor &amp;amp; Layout Improvements We&amp;rsquo;ve built a new editor that makes editing your content much easier and so much more enjoyable. We&amp;rsquo;ve also improved the app&amp;rsquo;s UI altogether.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Reasons Why Our New Editor Is Our Best Static Site Editor Yet</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/bigger-better-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 14:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/bigger-better-editor/</guid>
      <description>For the past few weeks, Nichlas and Nolan have been hard at work on the Forestry content editor. We wanted to make the easiest-to-use, most configurable static site content editor ever built. With their hard work, we now have some big improvements to share that get us that much closer. We’ve built a new and improved editor that makes managing your site easier and more effective than ever before. Both on the desktop and on mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Media Management</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/introducing-media-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 11:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/introducing-media-management/</guid>
      <description>We all love working with Markdown but one of it&amp;rsquo;s biggest limitations is adding images to your content. That&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce the Forestry.io Media Manager. Nolan and Nichlas put a lot of work into crafting an amazing UX for this, so we hope you like it. --
Media Manager Drag multiple files Handy if you have large image galleries.
Manage other files Also manage non-image files like PDFs, text files, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March 27th Service Outage</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/march-27th-service-outage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 21:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/march-27th-service-outage/</guid>
      <description>As some of you may have noticed, Forestry was down for about 2.5 hours between 23:00 UTC March 27 until 01:30 UTC March 28. In the spirit of full disclosure I&amp;rsquo;d like to explain what happened and why.
Forestry is a Rails application and from time to time the number of migrations we have get unwieldy. Being an application under rapid development, things are constantly changing and migrations are created sometimes daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customize the UI with Front Matter Templates</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/front-matter-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 10:47:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/front-matter-templates/</guid>
      <description>Does the following sound familiar? You set up a WP site, hand it off to a non-dev, and then they point to some unused part of the UI and say:
 &#34;What does this do?&#34;
 To which you sheepishly reply:
 &#34;Oh, that doesn&#39;t do anything...just ignore it.&#34;
 A CMS often feels like a work-around, designed for some other purpose.
Front Matter Templates (FMTs) FMTs allow you to customize the presentation of your UI fields in your CMS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Forestry.io</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/the-new-forestry-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 19:36:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/the-new-forestry-io/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce some huge improvements to Forestry.io, our CMS for Jekyll and Hugo sites.
Before I outline what&amp;rsquo;s new, I want to thank everyone who has been testing this while it was in beta (you know who you are). Your help was crucial and we&amp;rsquo;re going to continue to build an awesome CMS that you love. 👊
What&amp;rsquo;s new: New Editor We totally rebuilt our WYSIWYG editor (inspired by Medium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forestry &#43; GitLab</title>
      <link>https://forestry.io/blog/forestry-gitlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 23:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://forestry.io/blog/forestry-gitlab/</guid>
      <description>Now you can add a Forestry.io CMS to your GitLab.com static site (Jekyll or Hugo).
I&amp;rsquo;ve been a GitLab user since their very first release in Oct of 2011. I worked at a design agency and converted everything over from SVN to Git and used an internal GitLab installation. I remember submitting a few bugs and Dmitriy was quick to fix them. We loved GitLab then, and still do today.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>