<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sebastian Engels on pnyv dot sh</title>
    <link>/authors/sebastian-engels/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sebastian Engels on pnyv dot sh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>pnyv dot sh</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 14:00:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/authors/sebastian-engels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>uBuild: A New Jekyll Theme Using Blocks</title>
      <link>/blog/ubuild-a-new-theme-for-static-sites-using-blocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/ubuild-a-new-theme-for-static-sites-using-blocks/</guid>
      <description>Back in April we announced a feature that we believed was a game-changer for static site content managers. Blocks was here to introduce a way for you to put together sites using pre-composed site snippets inside Forestry.
While we did our best to show you how to set them up and give you an idea of how powerful they could be, we noticed that getting to know Blocks and figuring out how to set them up from scratch wasn&amp;rsquo;t as self-explanatory as we had hoped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Support for All Versions, Sorting for Pages and more</title>
      <link>/blog/hugo-support-sorting-for-pages-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 23:32:20 -1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/hugo-support-sorting-for-pages-and-more/</guid>
      <description>We just made a big change to how we handle Hugo projects and introduced a few new features that make it easier to stay organized.
Hugo Support for All Versions 🔥🔥🔥 Hugo has a great developer community that is constantly pushing new versions out. Until now you sometimes had to wait a few months until you were able to use the latest version of Hugo with Forestry as we were trying to catch up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Renaming Files and Improving Editing in a Team</title>
      <link>/blog/renaming-files-and-improving-team-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 04:39:03 -1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/renaming-files-and-improving-team-editing/</guid>
      <description>It’s a cloudy day ☁️ here on Prince Edward Island, the perfect opportunity to announce some new features.
Over the past couple weeks, we were hard at work to improve the editor experience for our Git-backed content manager. Renaming files is just one of those updates. We also needed to improve notifications and indicators to make working in a team on Forestry easier.
Renaming Files ✍️ Freshly out — you can now change the name for your content files with Forestry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudinary Integration, Data File Templates and Other Features</title>
      <link>/blog/cloudinary-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 15:12:40 -1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cloudinary-integration/</guid>
      <description>Image Transformation and Responsive Image Delivery Today we&amp;rsquo;re proud to announce an easy way to optimize your image delivery with a Cloudinary integration for Forestry.
As a developer you can now use the super fast Cloudinary CDN and store your assets outside your repository. While at the same time your editors can use Forestry&amp;rsquo;s Media Library and Editor to upload and manage Cloudinary assets without even knowing it.
It&amp;rsquo;s as simple as adding your cloud name, API key and secret to your site&amp;rsquo;s settings to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blocks - Give Your Editors the Power to Build Pages</title>
      <link>/blog/blocks-give-your-editors-the-power-to-build-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 14:41:00 -1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blocks-give-your-editors-the-power-to-build-pages/</guid>
      <description>Today we introduce Blocks - a powerful Field Type that enables your editors to build entire landing pages from scratch and create rich blog post layouts with a pre-defined code template, we call it a Block Template.
This feature was inspired by CraftCMS&amp;rsquo; Matrix fields and the Wordpress Plugin Advanced Custom Fields.
What is Blocks? Blocks is a Field Type that is made up of multiple templates, so-called Block Templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML File Contents are Moving to Plaintext Editor</title>
      <link>/blog/discontinuing-wysiwyg-editor-new-focus-on-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 21:57:29 -1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/discontinuing-wysiwyg-editor-new-focus-on-markdown/</guid>
      <description>We are not changing or removing the Markdown WYSIWYG editor. Our Markdown editor will continue to offer both plaintext and WYSIWYG input modes. In fact, removing the HTML WYSIWYG editor will allow us to focus on making the Markdown editor even better.
 The HTML WYSIWYG Editor has proven to be less and less the state-of-the-art content editing experience it once set out to be. Considering the issues the HTML WYSIWYG Editor causes and the merits Markdown provides we made the decision to discontinue our WYSIWYG HTML Editor on 5/11/2018.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>